Who taught you to wear makeup?
Do you have any idea
how bad this makeup is for your skin?
Everyone else is Preparing for the Gaokao.
Pucker up.
Going to school wearing makeup like this,
what would your teachers and classmates think?
Pucker them up.
Your lips.
Close your eyes.
You need to focus
on what matters—your studies.
Do you hear me?
It hurts.
Bear with it.
All done.
Take a look now.
So much prettier.
Mom's just doing this for your own good.
That's it for our date today.
About the question you just asked me...
Don't rush to answer.
Give yourself a little more time.
I'll give you my answer tomorrow.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Wait a minute.
Here.
I think
it's not as serious as you say.
It just means giving her more time.
We each just need to spare a bit.
It's not as easy as you say.
Have you ever thought about it?
They're not just dating.
They'll start a family in the future.
They'll even have kids.
And later on, the kids will go to school.
And they'll have to help them find jobs.
You're getting way ahead of yourself.
You're just being short-sighted.
Actually, I think
if we each squeeze out an hour or two,
it's totally doable.
That's enough for my workouts anyway.
Sure, it's enough for you,
but what about her makeup job?
Is she going to keep doing it?
Stop using others as an excuse.
I think
you're just worried about your game time.
Those crappy games of yours,
playing them or not makes no difference.
Oh, and your workouts are useful?
Will those muscles put food on the table?
They can't put food on the table,
but they're enough to crush your skull!
Maybe
us disappearing together
is the best choice.
You don't have to say that out of anger.
I'm serious.
Just like you said,
she'll get caught up in life's trifles,
but who knows,
that might be exactly what she wants.
The reason we exist
is because of past regrets.
If she loses Liang Chuan because of us,
wouldn't we repeat the same mistake?
It's not that I
refuse to give up my time.
But whether she really likes Liang Chuan,
we have no idea.
Yeah.
She has to decide this for herself.
Teacher Lin! Teacher Lin!
Are we drawing you again today?
Today,
you're drawing yourselves.
Let's talk.
The male lead is here.
Okay.
I've thought about it.
Thought about what?
You asked me yesterday,
out of the four Lin Ran personas,
which one I like best.
Right.
But I think that question
is fundamentally flawed.
Why?
To be honest,
sometimes I really wonder
if, at a certain moment,
you were actually possessed by someone.
But I quickly dismissed that idea.
Do you know why?
Because I've always believed
that you are just you.
Even though at different times,
your temper and habits might differ,
but
your earnestness,
persistence,
and gentleness
have never changed.
When did you figure that out?
From your gaze.
When I look into your eyes,
I can feel it.
My gaze?
What kind of gaze did you give him?
The same as yours.
So,
you doubt there are four Lin Ran personas.
But you're special.
Like four Lin Ran from other timelines
sharing the same body.
Then let me ask a different question.
Even if there are four Lin Ran personas,
there must be one you prefer to be with.
What are you hoping for?
Nothing.
If I had to choose,
I think I'd choose the original Lin Ran.
Let's go, let's go.
Where were you?
We missed you.
Move, move. Make way.
I just don't know how to face you all.
You don't need to know how to face us.
Now, you only need to face one person.
He already gave you his answer.
Go on.
I haven't figured it out yet.
Cut the nonsense.
Let's go. Move, move, move.
Where did you go?
I...
I just saw the principal walking by,
so I said hello.
The question you asked me earlier...
I already answered it.
Can I ask you a question?
Would you like to officially date me?
I...
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Why?
Because I'm not ready yet
to take on the responsibilities,
nor am I ready to lose what I have.
I have a condition.
Don't talk. Don't talk.
What condition?
Two people together need to compromise.
I agree with that.
But I don't want to lose myself.
Most of the time,
I'll be the Teacher Lin you know well.
But at certain moments,
if I really want to play games,
if I want to work out,
or if I want to continue my makeup career,
you have to support me.
And respect me.
Can you do that?
Is that your only condition?
Yes, that's it.
I agree.
I like you exactly the way you are now.
You don't need to change a thing.
Lin Ran.
I like how in everything you do,
you always try your hardest.
So...
I guess we're officially dating.
Alright.
Did you ask?
He's really not going to the internet cafe?
I told you, we made plans to go hiking.
Hiking?
I'm good at that!
I'll definitely Crush him!
Bro, they're going on a date.
It's not a boot camp.
All you think about is working out.
All right, all right.
Give it a rest, both of you.
We agreed today it's just the two of us.
Just the two of us are going.
Wait, are you Ditching friends for love?
Plus, you're a bit ungrateful too.
What are you even talking about?
Don't you forget.
We're also among the people he likes.
Just speak for yourself.
Don't drag me into this.
All right.
Does this look good?
It looks good.
I'm going to get changed then.
So beautiful.
Do you guys think they'll kiss today?
What should we do next?
Let's walk over there.
Sure.
Do you want to kiss?
Come over here.
Alright.
I think I lost my bag.